tutorials-expert.com 2010-12-31

# Privacy Policy

We greatly respect your privacy and we hope that our users feel that the information they share with us is 100% secure and private or within our small community here at tutorials-expert. Given below are a few guidelines we follow to ensure your privacy and our integrity:

### Registration

In order to use this website to the full potential, we highly recommend that you become a user. During registration a user is required to give their e-mail address, name, and other optional identifiers. This information is to identify the user, and for other users to interact with the user. None of this information will be sold, transmitted, or in any other way sent to any third parties. You also may be asked for your location, instant messenger names, etc but these are only optional and you may leave them empty.

### Cookies

Cookies are used to identify the user when he/she logs in, and for tracking purposes. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user�s hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. The main reason for using cookies is that a user doesn't have to enter password everytime he/she visits us.

### Passwords

We will NEVER ask for your password. If someone does ask for your password or other info, please immediately notify us.

### Log Files

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user�s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

### Links

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website.

### Surveys & POLLS

From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or POLLS. Participation in these surveys or POLLS is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information.

### Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on the news so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an e-mail. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

### Final Notes

Please understand that we will never, under any circumstances give away or displays your IP address. Additionally, we will never sell or transmit e-mail addresses or any other personal identifiers to 3rd parties. Use of the registration system is optional; however it does maximize the user's experience here at the site.

If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please do not hesitate to Contact Us! Thank you for your cooperation.
